ferret.com.au 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy

* ## We care about your privacy.

At Cirrus Media, we‘re committed to protecting your personal information. That’s why we’ve put together this policy. It explains in simple terms what kind of personal information we collect, how we use it and whether we disclose it to anyone else. And because we take privacy seriously, it’s been designed with careful reference to the Australian Privacy Principles (APPs) and related privacy laws. 

This policy applies to the Cirrus Media Group Companies, including Cirrus Media Pty Ltd (“Cirrus Media”, “we”, “us”, “our”) and its related bodies corporate. 

* ##  Collection of personal information

Personal information is information or an opinion about an identified individual or an individual who is reasonably identifiable. We usually collect personal information directly from individuals. However, we may also collect personal information about individuals from various third parties (for more details, see ‘Handling of personal information’ below). 

The type of personal information we collect depends upon your relationship with us. When doing business with us, you may need to prove your identity and in some cases, the law requires you to do so. We may also require your contact information so that we can communicate with you directly or deliver products and services to you. So the information we collect for these purposes might include your name, telephone number, email address, business address, employment information and possibly, your driver’s licence or some other form of photo identification. 

Less often we might collect personal information about you in connection with a commercial trading account or financing arrangement (such as bank records, credit card statements, credit reporting information), particularly if you’re intending to enter into the arrangement in your own name. We’ll provide you with more detailed information about exactly how this type of information will be used and who it may be disclosed to prior to collection. 

At times we may also collect personal information for quality and improvement purposes, such as voice recordings made to our call centre and customer satisfaction surveys. 

Whenever it’s appropriate, we’ll offer you the opportunity to interact with us anonymously or by a different name. Commonly this option will be provided to you when making a general enquiry about our products and services or requesting information about a job opportunity. 

* ##  Handling of personal information

We will do our utmost to ensure that your personal information is only used and/or disclosed for the purpose it was collected, or a related purpose that’s within your reasonable expectations. 

  * From time to time we may need to disclose personal information to, or collect information about individuals from various third parties, including: other companies within the Cirrus Media group of companies
  * credit providers (disclosed and undisclosed)
  * information technology providers
  * data processing and payment providers
  * financial services and banking providers
  * consultancy firms and independent contractors
  * auditors, lawyers and other professional service firms
  * marketing agencies and other marketing services providers
  * print/mail/digital/imaging/document management service providers
  * customer, product, business or strategic research and development organisations
  * data partners and analytics consultants
  * publicly available sources of information
  * other entities, as required or authorised by law

Some of these third parties may be located overseas. 

And to help safeguard your privacy, we’ll impose requirements on these entities for handling personal information. We’ll also do our best to inform you at or before the time of collection, about the types of organisations we may be disclosing your personal information to. 

In addition to the above, personal information may be provided to other parties where you specifically consent. 

* ##  Marketing

Every now and again you may be contacted by mail, SMS, telephone, email or online so that we can inform you about new products and services, promotions, offers, newsletters, customer surveys competitions and the like. We may also engage third parties to do this on our behalf. In so far as the law allows us to, we are likely to market to you unless you tell us otherwise. Equally, we’ll always give you the opportunity to “opt-out” of direct marketing communications. If you don’t want to be contacted for marketing purposes, you don’t have to wait to be contacted. Simply advise us in any one of the methods set out below and we will make every effort to meet your request as soon as practicable. 

* ##  Our use of Cookies and other technologies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. Cirrus Media uses cookies to make your use of our websites and services as convenient as possible. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s browser. Cookies are useful to estimate our number of users and determine overall traffic patterns through our website. Cirrus Media also uses other technologies such as Catchbot to collect data. Bots are a type of web crawler that browse the internet for the purpose of web indexing and updating web content. 

If you do not wish to receive any cookies or bots you may set your browser to refuse cookies or bots. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of Cirrus Media’s services. 

**Google cookies**  
Cirrus Media uses Google Analytics features (including Google Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting) on our website. We, and some third parties (including Google), use both first party and third party cookies to record standard internet traffic information to optimise ad selection based on age, gender, interests and past visits to our site; evaluate your interactions with ad services on our site; and serve targeted advertising on sites across the Internet. 

We, and some third parties (including Google), also use first and third party cookies to optimise advertising on our websites. 

Importantly, we do not combine the anonymous information collected through Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. 

To opt out of these features at any time, simply change your Google Ads Settings by [http://networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed](http://google.com.au/policies/technologies/ads)). 

If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. However, this will mean that we will not be able to personalise your website each time you visit. 

* ##  Security of personal information

Once we have collected your personal information, we’ll take reasonable steps to ensure it is protected against misuse, loss, interference, unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. We do this in a variety of ways, including maintaining physical security of paper and electronic data stores (such as locks, security systems) and appropriate computer and network security (such as firewalls, user identification policies, encryption, password controls). Your personal information is stored and held securely by third party data storage providers used by Cirrus Media. 

* ##  Destruction of personal information

We’ll destroy or de-identify personal information that is no longer needed, provided there is no law requiring us to retain it. 

* ##  Access to and correction of personal information

Whilst we have processes in place to make sure your personal information is accurate and up-to-date, we welcome your requests to access and/or correct information we hold about you. To make a request, simply contact us in one of the ways set out below. There are no set charges for making a request, however we may charge a fee if need be, to recover any reasonable costs associated with responding to your request. 

* ##  Collection notice: Booking forms

This following information relates specifically to the personal information we collect from our event booking forms. Such information will generally include the names, and contact details of event delegates or sponsors, as well as information about the particular industry sector in which they operate and general billing information. 

We use this information for the primary purpose of registering delegates for the events we organise, and administering the attendance and participation of both sponsors and delegates. 

If we do not collect the information requested on the booking forms, we may not be able to process an individual’s attendance at an event. 

With your consent, we may also share your information with other entities [so that they can contact you about future event opportunities that may be of interest to you. 

Please see paragraphs 8 and 10 for details as to how you can access and correct the personal information we collect from our booking forms, or make a complaint about our handling of such information. 

We do not disclose personal information collected from our booking forms to recipients located outside Australia. 

* ##  Contact Us and complaints

For more information about our privacy practices, make a complaint or lodge a request under this policy, please contact: 

The Privacy Officer 

Cirrus Media Pty Limited  
Phone: +612 8484 0888   
Email: privacy@cirrusmedia.com.au   
Mail: Cirrus Media Pty Limited,   
Tower 2 475 Victoria Ave or Locked Bag 2999 Chatswood DC,   
Chatswood NSW 2067 

We will endeavour to respond to your request or complaint within 30 days. If you are still not satisfied, you may take your complaint to the OAIC. 

* ##  Application of this Privacy Policy

This policy applies to the following websites: 

  * **Cirrus Media Main Site**
  * cirrusmedia.com.au
  * **Other sites**
  * mediakit.moneymanagement.com.au
  * australiandoctorlive.com
  * awards.bandt.com.au
  * events.moneymanagement.com.au
  * primeawards.com.au
  * cx-transformation.com.au
  * digital-storytelling.com.au
  * franchiseawards.net.au
  * franchiseawards.net.au
  * fundmanagerawards.com.au
  * gpsmakethedifference.com.au
  * awards.lawyersweekly.com.au
  * madweek.com.au
  * mining-productivity.com.au
  * mmleaderseries.com.au
  * postretirementforum.com.au
  * ruraldoctorseminar.com.au
  * roadshows.travelweekly.com.au
  * womeninfinance.moneymanagement.com.au
  * womeninindustry.com.au
  * investmentplatforms.com.au
  * medobs.com.au
  * mydr.com.au
  * fst.net.au
  * medicalmedia.com.au
  * encoredirectory.com.au
  * aards.com.au
  * eguide.com.sg
  * just4docs.com.au
